Jessica Yeung

858.397.8092

JYEUNG2838@GMAIL.COM

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/JESSICAJYEUNG

JESSICAJYEUNG.GITHUB.IO

ABOUT ME

I am a practicing **designer** motivated by user research in technology advancement and health. At UC San Diego, I am learning **Human-Centered Design** and **Interaction**. My project engineering skills, diligence, and eagerness to learn allows me to be an asset on your team.

EXPERIENCE

MARKETING & PUBLIC RELATIONS DEPUTY

UCSD Tzu Chi Collegiate (Sept. 2017 - June 2018)

Increasing awareness of Tzu Ching's chapter's mission, footprints, and fundraiser efforts by promoting and spreading social media posts to members. Participating in collective ASL performances at charity events.

EXECUTIVE AND PUBLICITY OFFICER

Muir Art Club (January 2017 - June 2018)

Collaborating with team of three other Executive Officers to coordinate, and host de-stressing crafting events.

Conducted surveys, handled the budget, organized inventory, created graphic designs for events, and publicized events online.

CONVERSATION LEADER

UCSD Extension (June 2016 - Present)

Engaging groups of international students in conversations to improve their English speaking and listening proficiency. Assisting administration during new student registration and campus tours.

UX RESEARCHER

G.A.T.E Center (October 2017 - December 2017)

Designed the G.A.T.E. Center as a transitional and education center on autonomous vehicles as a solution to the increasing awareness and unease of an automated society in San Diego. Conducted user field studies, and prototyped an experiential design. D4SD 2017 Finalist.

EDUCATION UC SAN DIEGO

Expected Graduation in June 2018

Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Science Specialization in HCI, Design and Interaction

CURRENT PROJECT

GARDENING CURRICULUM, UCSD GLOBAL TIES INITIATIVE

Currently designing a gardening curriculum for Mundo's Community Garden in National City to teach and engage children from ages 5-10 about sustainability through gardening to increase awareness of personal wellness.

Skills Tools

Affinity Mapping	Design Thinking
Field Studies	Excel
Heuristic Evaluation	Gantt Chart
Information Hierarchy	Figma
Journey Mapping	Google Drive
Moodboards	Invision App
Prototyping	Marvel App
Story Boarding	Outlook
User Interviews	PowerPoint
User Personas	UXPin
Usability Testing	Word
Wireframing	

I am proud of

transferring to UC San Diego speaking Cantonese, Mandarin, and Japanese

learning how to do basic web development enjoying swimming, hiking, and meditating my friends and family